Hello, Sakura-chan.
こんにちは、さくろちゃん
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You look so young, how old are you now?
すんげー若そうに見えるけどさ、今何歳なの?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
18 years old.
18歳
This smiling face.
ニコニコしてるこの笑顔
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいじゃん
I'm a junior high school student.
中学生なんだ
Until recently, I was a high school student.
ついこの間まで高校生だ
that's right.
そうです
That's amazing.
すごいね
Wow, it looks tiny though.
すごい、あとちっちゃそうに見えるけど
How old are you tall?
身長何歳?
Something like 149 years old.
149歳とか
149 years old.
149歳
I'm not 50 years old.
50歳ないんだ
No.
ないです
It's chibi.
ちびじゃん
It's Chibi-chan.
おちびちゃんだね
That's amazing.
すごいな
It's cute.
かわいいね
It suits you, your height.
似合ってるよ、その身長
How many cup breasts?
胸何カップ?
It's an E cup.
Eカップです
Eカップなんだ
She looks so young.
こんななんか幼い顔だもん
You have a naughty body.
エッチな体してるんだね
perhaps.
たぶん
So what do you usually do?
じゃあいつもは何してるの?
Holidays, etc.
休日とか
I just lounge around at home and watch TV.
お家でゴロゴロしてテレビとか見てます
Do you like TV?
テレビ好きなの?
That's rare.
珍しいね
It's not usually YouTube,
普通YouTubeとかじゃない、
The current generation.
今の世代は
It's true that there are many families like this around me.
たしかに、周りはみんな結構そういう家の方が多いかも
Sakura-chan is a TV person.
さくらちゃんはテレビ派なんだね
TV fan.
テレビ派
Well then, you're with your uncle.
じゃあ、おじさんと一緒だね
That's right.
そっかそっか
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏はいるの?
You don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏はいないね
Isn't there?
ないの?
Even though she seems to have everything, she doesn't have many boyfriends.
なんでもなもてそうなのに、彼氏少ない
I had quite a few encounters.
なかなか出会いが
Don't you come across it unexpectedly?
意外に出会いないの?
No.
ないです
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
It's such a waste.
すごいもったいないね
How many people have you experienced so far?
今まで経験人数は何人だ?
2 people?
2人?
There's only two of us.
2人しかいないんだ
I'm not happy about it at all, then.
全くもうけがれてないね、そしたらね
I'll be the third person today.
今日で3人目になっちゃうけど
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
I will.
するよね
So, what type of guy do you like?
じゃあ、男の人で好きなタイプは?
I think it would be nice to have someone who is kind and tolerant.
優しくて、包容力がある人がいいなって思います
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
So, is it okay to say that I like old men?
じゃあ、もうおじさん好きってことでいいかな?
But I like older people better.
でも、年上の人の方が好き
yes?
そう?
It's impossible to be around the same age.
同い年ぐらいは無理だ
There were at least 3 spots apart.
最低でも3個ぐらいは離れてた
Hey, that's right.
へ ー、そうなんだ
I want you to pull me out, see you then.
引っ張ってほしいんだね、じゃあね
I see.
なるほどね
Even if Sakura-chan's appearance draws me in a lot.
このさくらちゃんの見た目でぐいぐい引っ張られてもね
What are you happiest doing?
何してるときが一番幸せ?
When I'm watching TV and when I'm eating.
テレビ見てるときと、ご飯食べてると
What do you like to eat?
ご飯は何好きなの?
Yakiniku.
焼肉
Yakiniku?
焼肉?
It feels like you could call it a salad, but...
サラダとか言いそうな感じなんだけど、
Did you wear yakiniku?
焼肉着たか
Everyone likes meat, right?
肉はみんな好きなんだね、そしたらね
Well then, Sakura-chan.
じゃあ、さくらちゃん
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみてよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
The transparency of this skin.
この肌の透明感
People say you have beautiful skin, right?
肌きれいって言われるでしょ?
It is said.
言われます
That's what I'm told.
言われるよね
It's really beautiful, really.
すごいきれいだもん、本当に
Can you turn around?
後ろ向いてごらん?
Try raising that Muscat a bit.
そのマスカートちょっと上上げてみてよ
Please turn around here.
こっち振り向いてごらん
You're wearing cute pants.
かわいいパンツはいってるね
Those pants look good on you.
似合うね、そのパンツ
It looked like she was actually an idol, but I couldn't see her that way.
本当アイドルとかいそうだけど、そういう見ちゃいかなかったんだ
Yo.
よ
It didn't happen.
い かなかった
yes.
そう
Thanks to you for not going, now...
行かないでくれたおかげで、今ね、
Because my butt is taken off.
お尻取れてるから
That's lucky for me.
こっちとしてはラッキーだよね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Okay, everyone turn this way.
いいよ、全部向いてこっち
You can just turn this way.
こっち向いちゃっていいよ
I also lowered my skirt.
スカートも下げちゃって
It’s been a long time since you’ve been touched by a man?
男の人に触られるのはすごい久しぶり?
That's right.
だよね
Kuru-chan, please go next door.
くるちゃん、じゃあ隣行って
Stretch it out slowly.
上ゆっくり伸ばしてごらん
big.
大きい
Breasts?
お っぱい?
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Even though her style is slim, her boobs are big.
スタイル細いのに、おっぱいだけ大きいんだね
Those are miraculous breasts.
奇跡のおっぱいじゃん
I'm embarrassed.
照れちゃう
Really stylish.
本当にスタイリー
Just turn back.
そのまま後ろ向いて
Kuru-chan, take off your skirt.
くるちゃん、スカート取っちゃって
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Why do you have such a face and such a naughty body?
なんでこんな顔でこんなエッチな体してるの?
Your smile is cute.
笑顔かわいいね
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Try pushing those pants into your butt.
そのパンツさ、お尻に自分で食い込ませてみて
can?
できる?
That's no good.
それじゃダメ
Lots more.
もっといっぱい
I got as much T-whack as I could.
思いっきりいっぱいTワックにしちゃって
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Just the face.
顔だけ
There's a huge gap between the body and the face.
体と顔、すごいギャップあるね
You've never been taken like this before.
こんなに取られたことないでしょ
I'm getting nervous.
緊張しちゃうね
Can I look at Sakura-chan's cute breasts?
さくらちゃんのかわいいおっぱい見ていいかな?
Then.
そしたら
Sakura-chan, take that off.
さ くらちゃん、それ外しちゃって
Remove it slowly.
ゆっくり外して
These are amazingly erotic breasts.
すごいエロいおっぱい、これ
Those are the breasts that only two people have ever touched.
今まで2人しか触ってないおっぱいでしょ
The shape and color are amazing.
形も色も、すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look at your pants.
パンツ見てごらん
Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃん
Your hair is so smooth.
お毛、ツルツルなんだね
Is that so?
そうなの?
The style is really nice, really.
スタイルはすごくいいよ、本当に
Are you exercising?
運動してるの?
I used to do it.
昔やってた
Are you not doing it now?
今はしてないの?
But she has such an erotic body.
なのにこんなエロい体してるんだ
Just sit there.
そこに座ってごらん
Come to gymnastics.
体操でおいで
Open your legs.
足開いて
get nervous?
緊張する?
Please open it more.
もっと開いてごらん
Are you laughing?
笑っちゃう?
Open this yourself.
これ自分で開いてごらん
Hold the lower part.
もっと下の方を持って
Please stick your butt out more.
もっとお尻こっちに突き出してごらん
Do your best to open it.
それ頑張って開いて
Your pussy is so small.
おまんこすごいちっちゃいね
Chin-chan, are you coming in?
ちんちゃん、入るの?
this.
これ
I'll probably go in.
多分入る
Kuro-chan, please help me.
くろちゃん手伝ってあげて
Open more.
もっと開いて
I'm against it.
反対です
Will Kuro-chan's dick fit in here?
くろちゃんのちんちんこれ入るかな?
Dokuro-chan?
どうくろちゃん?
It looks really tight.
すげーきつそうだよ
It's like showing even your butt hole.
お尻の穴まで見せる感じで
You can even see my stomach.
お腹まで見えてる
I've never seen it myself.
自分でも見たことない
Kuro-chan, please touch my chestnut.
くろちゃん、くりちょっと触ってみて
Where do you touch women all the time?
いつも女にするとこはさ、どこ触ってんの?
There?
そこ?
So, can I ask Kuro-chan to touch me?
じゃあくろちゃんに触ってもらっていい?
It always feels good there.
いつもそこが気持ちいいんだ
Then stand up.
そしたらさ、立ってごらん
Kuro-chan, come next to me.
くろちゃん隣に来て
Can I stare at this cute face?
この可愛い顔を注視していい?
Then.
そしたら
good?
いい?
I'll do it right.
ちゃんするよ
You look so naughty, Kuro-chan.
すごいエッチな顔するね、くろちゃん
Serve it to me.
したべーって出して
Next time Kuro-chan will be exposed.
今度くろちゃんぶろ出して
Try this Sakura-chan.
これさくらちゃんつってみて
Sakura-chan, it's been a while since I last had Chinese food.
どうさくらちゃん、久しぶりの中華
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
Does it feel a little good?
ちょっと気持ちいい?
Do you feel erotic?
エロい気分になる?
Kuro-chan slowly touches her breasts.
くろちゃんゆっくりおっぱい触ってもらう
soft?
柔らかい?
Can you feel my nipples?
乳首が感じる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Kuro-chan's left nipple is boring.
くろちゃん左手の乳首つまんないんだ
You look so cute
すごい可愛い顔するじゃ
yeah.
ん
You can lick it, just like that.
舐 めていいよ、そのまま
Did you get your nipples blown?
乳首ビンビンしたんじゃ?
Sakura-chan, did you take off her nipples?
さくらちゃん乳首取ってんじゃ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Did you stand up?
立っちゃった?
Erotic
エロ
stomach?
い?
Did you stand up too?
そ っちも立った?
Kuro-chan.
くろちゃん
Both nipples are erect.
両方の乳首ビンビン立ってるじゃん
You can see it, right?
見てわかるでしょ?
You can tell by looking at it.
見てもわかるじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
This time, I asked her to raise her armpits and hold me above her elbows.
今度は脇あげてもらって、肘上で抱えて
do not have.
ない
Kuro-chan, let me give you a chew.
くろちゃん、チューしてもらう
Clean everything up.
全部きれいにしてあげて
How does it feel to be on the sidelines?
脇ながらにどんな感じ?
The feeling for the first time.
初めての感覚
A feeling like this for the first time?
初 めての感覚?
Just leave it here and put it on top of this.
そのままこっちなし、この上に乗っけてよ
Kuro-chan, it's so popular that it's grown.
くろちゃん、人気でくりどりして
Kuro-chan is doing a really naughty pose.
くろちゃん、すごいエッチなポーズしてるよ
You can talk to your breasts.
おっぱいに喋っていいよ
Kuro-chan.
く ろちゃん
Kuro-chan, please sit down.
くろちゃん、座ってもらおう
You know what this is?
これなんだ、わかる?
I understand.
わかる
correct answer.
正解
Touch me from above your pants.
パンツの上から触って
Let me pet you
なでなでしてもらお
cormorant.
う
I happened to have you touch the bottom as well.
下 もたまたま全部触ってもらお
cormorant.
う
Has it gradually expanded?
ちょっと ずつ膨らんできた?
Put your hand under his pants and squeeze his dick.
パンツの下から手を入れて、 ちんちん握ってみて
Take out your pants
パンツを出してみ
hand.
て
Bring your face closer.
も っと顔を近づけて
How does it make you feel?
どんな気分になる?
It makes me feel really good.
めっちゃ気分になっちゃう
I just poked it with my finger
指でさっきポツンズンしてみ
hand.
て
I'm touching everything
全部 触ってるで
Sho?
しょ?
Are you excited?
興 奮する?
I just tried potsunzun
さっきポツンズンしてみ
hand.
て
Isn't it bigger than Sakura's face?
さ くらちゃんの顔より大きいんじゃない?
The face that's being hit by the dick is so cute.
ちんちん当てられてる顔めっちゃ可愛いね
Rub it in more.
もっといっぱいこすりつけて
Put it on the edges.
ふちびりにはつけて
Hold it in your hand, blow it up, and lick it by chance.
それ手で持って、 ふいあげてたまたまなめてみて
Have you ever licked here?
ここ舐めたことある?
A man?
男の人の?
first time.
初めて
So why don't you try licking it a lot?
じゃあいっぱい舐めてあげてみる?
I opened my mouth and happened to snap it.
口開けてたまたまパクって
Put it in your mouth?
口の中入れてみ?
Put it all in.
全部入れて
It's starting to become bellows from the bottom.
下からベローンってなってきて
Take out your tongue.
ベロ出して
Temporarily all.
仮全部なって
It makes noise.
音を立てるんです
A very naughty voice came out.
すごいエッチな声出てきた
Chin chin.
ちんちん
This is a strawberry bear.
チゴのクマで入ってるね、これ
painful?
苦しい?
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
Kuru-chan, sit down.
くるちゃん、座って
Lick this.
これ舐めて
I'm drooling and jerking off with my hands.
唾垂らして、手でしごいところ
You're wet and naughty, dick.
濡れ濡れのエッチだね、ちんちん
Do it sooner.
もっと早くして
Is Chin-chan delicious?
ちんちゃん美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
Lift it up from below.
下 からつきあげて
This Sakura-chan is so cute.
このさくらちゃん、しめしょっか
Then let's go to bed.
じゃあベッド行こう
Sakura-chan, please try to sleep.
さくらちゃん、お寝てみて
Talk about mellow breasts.
めろいおっぱい喋って
Look, you can lick her boobs.
見てみ、おっぱい舐められると
The opposite Earth is pinched.
反対の地球つまんでくる
Be stiff.
こりこりして
Gradually lick the bottom part.
だんだん下の方まで舐めてきて
Try opening it.
開いてみして
A very beautiful mango.
すっごい綺麗なマンゴー
It's embarrassing to be photographed with mangoes so close.
こんな近くでマンゴー撮られて恥ずかしいね
Let me hold it on my feet.
自分で足上に抱えてもらおう
You can see all the way to the hole inside.
中の穴まで丸見える
Look, it's being licked.
見てみ、舐められてると
Lick it all from below.
全部舐めてあげて、下から
While widening the hole.
穴広げながら
Insert the entire bottom into the hole.
穴に下全部入れて
Just spit it out.
そのまま吐き回して
Sakura-chan, do you understand?
さくらちゃん、分かる?
Enter the bottom into the mango.
下をマンゴーに入って
Do you understand?
分かる?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Everything from the butthole up.
お 尻の穴から上まで全然
Did you lick every nook and cranny?
隅々全部舐めた?
I want to take a picture of the mango being licked.
マンゴー舐められてるから撮っておきたい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Thrust downward.
下突っ込む
She has a really erotic voice.
すんごいエロい声出てるよ
I stabbed a lot.
いっぱい刺した
Spread it out.
広げにして
Sakura-chan, have you ever used a phone when trying to get a woman?
さくらちゃん、女にするとき電話使ったことある?
So, can I try using it?
じゃあ、使ってみていい?
Tighten your cleat.
クリートリスを締めてあげて
around the hole
穴のあたり
To.
に
Because my clitoris is getting bigger.
ク リートリス大きくなってきたから
Try opening it sometime.
何かのうちに開けてみて
Aren't you going in?
入るんじゃない?
this.
これ
It's small.
小さいね
It's really tough.
すんごいきつい
My phone got stuck.
電話刺さっちゃったよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I took it kind of slowly though.
なんかゆっくりかけましたけど
Look, it's all the way down to the roots.
ほ ら、根元まで入ってる
Do you understand?
わかる?
Properly.
ちゃんと
Are you trembling inside?
中で震えてる?
Maybe you feel it.
感じてるかも
cute.
かわいい
Hold my legs.
足抱えて
This is slimy inside.
中ぬるぬるだね、これ
If you have such a cute face, you must be a pervert.
こんなかわいい顔したら、変態じゃん
I'll open it up and bring it to you.
ひらげて持ってくるじゃん
My pussy is twitching.
おまんこひくひくしてるよ
Kura-chan, please try calling again.
くらちゃん、もう一回電話してみて
Doesn't it feel good?
くり気持ちいいでしょ?
Kura-chan, aim for the chestnut.
くらちゃん、くり狙ってごらん
She has a really naughty face.
すんごいいやらしい顔してる
Try expanding it.
ひろげてみしてみ
hand.
て
I'm going to go crazy.
い っちゃいちゃう
I'm patient, I'm patient to the limit.
ガマンだよ、限界までガマンしてる
Well, let's go and look again.
じゃあ、行くとこ、もう一回見してみて
Kura-chan is expanding.
くらちゃん、ひろげておる
It's amazing, my pussy is twitching.
すんごいじゃん、まんこひくひくしてる
It's gone.
いっちゃったね
You were moving your hips a lot, right now.
すんごい腰動いてたね、今ね
Use something more erotic.
もっとエロいやつ使って
What do you think?
どうかな?
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見た
Will it fit this big foot?
こんなでっかいフットン入るかな?
A day bigger than Sakura-chan's face.
さくらちゃんの顔よりでっかい1日
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
Shall I try it once?
一回入れてみるか
Put your feet on it and hold me.
足それ上にして、抱えてくれ
Please insert it slowly.
ゆっくりぶち込んでごらん
That's tight, pussy.
きっついね、おまんこ
It's full of dicks, isn't it?
ちんちんでいっぱいでしょ
Inside your nose.
鼻の中
It's too tight and there are no pressure points.
きつすぎてつぼつぼなんないね
Her pussy is so tight.
おまんこパンパンだもん
Try something that spins around.
ぐるぐるするやつやってみて
So I stirred the pussy as it was.
それでおまんこのままかきまわして
Do you know that I'm wanted?
ほしくられてるのわかる?
copper?
どう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Pull it out slowly and stab it.
ゆっくり抜き刺して
Put that far in.
そこまで入れて
You have such an erotic face.
すごいエロい顔して
Make it the hole you pulled out.
抜いた穴にして
It's tough.
きついな
Get your hands wet.
手を濡らして
Touch the top of me once where it feels good.
上の気持ちいいところ1回触ってあげてほら
Touch all the way down to the pussy.
下のほうまでまんこ全部触って
Touch all the walls.
全部の壁触ってあげて
Spread your fingers in the right places.
そ んまいところで指広げて
Stimulate the upper part.
上のほうを刺激して
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Her pleasant face is also very cute.
気持ちいい顔もすごいかわいいな
Show me more.
もっと見せてみろ
Finally open it and show me.
最後開いて見せて
Kuro-chan, you want to be attacked, right?
くろちゃん、攻められたいでしょ
Lay your head over here.
頭こっちに寝てほら
Kakara-chan, wake up.
かからちゃん、起きて
Come on, bring your face closer.
ちんちん顔近づけてほら
Get between my legs.
足の間に入って
Touch it with your hands.
手で触って
Just put the small ones in your mouth.
ちっちゃいものは口くわえてほら
Make it bigger with your mouth.
口で大きくしてほら
Do your hands.
手とかして
My dick is getting bigger.
ちんちん大きくなってきたよ
Say Perron from below.
下からペローンって言って
Take your dick.
ちんちん持って
Please make me feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしてあげて
By chance.
たまたまもんで
Drop with saliva.
唾でーっと垂らして
Suck it there.
そこでしゃぶって
Kuro-chan, be patient.
くろちゃん、我慢だよ
Try eating it all the way to the bottom.
一番奥まで食えてみて
The deepest part there?
そこ一番奥?
Try adding more.
もっと入れてみて
painful?
苦しい?
Kuro-chan also licked her pussy.
くろちゃんもおまんこ舐めてあげて
Put it on top of Kuro-chan's face.
おまんこくろちゃんの顔の上に乗っけて
Move your hips and rub against it.
自分で腰を動かしてすりつけてほら
Suck my dick.
ちんちんしゃぶって
Kuro-chan, suck it a lot.
くろちゃんいっぱいしゃぶってほら
Drink the whole manjiri.
まんじり全部飲んで
Put your hair back.
髪を後ろにして
Your dick is delicious.
おちんちんおいしいですわ
My dick is delicious.
おちんちんおいしいです
Just with your mouth.
口だけで
Then just add it to the back.
それで奥まで加えばいい
So leave it there.
それで置いて
Licking people.
人をペロペロして
Leave it in your mouth.
口に加えたまま
Licking me from the side.
横からペロペロってやって
Bumpy in your mouth?
口になくパンパン?
all.
全部
Fill it with blood.
血をいっぱいして
Should I include Kuro-chan too?
くろちゃんも入れちゃおうか
Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃん
Why don't you put your dick in yourself?
ちんちん自分で入れてみ?
Get on top.
上に乗って
Can I put it in?
入れれる?
By yourself.
自分で
You haven't been on top of it much, have you?
あんまり上に乗ったことないでしょ?
Take a look.
見してみなよ
Her pussy is so tight that there's no sound.
おまんこきつくて音がないんだじゃん
Just put it in slowly.
ゆっくり入れてってほら
Chinchindo?
ちんちんどう?
Isn't your pussy tight?
まんこパンパンでしょ?
I crashed my bike.
バイクをすりつけた
Sakura-chan is deeply penetrated.
さくらちゃんズボズボ刺さってるよ
Look at all those pleasant faces.
気持ちいい顔いっぱい見してほら
Squeeze it yourself.
自分でくしぐってほら
Stab yourself.
自分でちんちん刺して
Your face with a penis in it is cute.
ちんちん入ってる顔かわいいね
Try putting it all the way in?
一番奥まで入れてみ?
Rub it on.
すりつけて
Can you make it look like an M letter on top of that?
その上でM字みたくできる?
Get on your knees.
膝立てて
So why not hit it?
それで打ちつけてみ?
Chin chin.
ちんちん
Can you see the butt's sting?
ぶっといの刺さってるの見える?
It's so big.
すんごいぶっくり
Look behind me.
手後ろについてほら
Kuro-chan, wake up.
くろちゃん起きて
Place it on top of Kuro-chan.
くろちゃんの上に置いてほら
They find each other and follow each other.
見つけ合いながらついてしまう
Then, this time, Kuro-chan objected.
そしたら今度、くろちゃん反対
Sakura-chan rides M-shaped on top of this.
さくらちゃんこの上にM字乗って
Kuro-chan, you're not taking it easy.
くろちゃんゆっくり置いてないでしょ
It was dripping all over my manjiri.
まんじりいっぱい垂れてきたよ
Stretch your hips.
腰を伸ばして
Go faster and faster.
だんだん早くしてほら
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
もっとくろちゃん早く
Look, it's all puffy.
パンパンついてほら
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
I can't resist it yet.
まだ我慢ないけど
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
くろちゃんもっと早く
Kuro-chan slowly once again.
くろちゃんゆっくりもう一回
Just tease me.
いったまんこいじめろ
I went off twice.
2回もちんちんでいっちゃった
Look, I'm slumbering.
よつんぼになってほら
It must have been very fast.
いったかもすごい早いじゃん
Next time, Kuro-chan, please stop.
今度くろちゃん止まってほら
Lower yourself and see.
自分で腰下げてほら
Penis yourself.
自分でちんちん
What's going on with your dick?
ちんちんどうなってる?
You like hard dicks, right?
固いちんちん好きでしょ?
like.
好き
Follow Kuro-chan.
くろちゃんついて
Put your hands behind your back.
手を後ろにしてほら
Just follow me now.
そんまもういっきりついてほら
Open your pussy and see.
おまんこ開いてみしてほら
Pussy with penis.
ちんちんでいったまんこ
There's a hole in it.
穴ぽっからいてんじゃん
Look at me sideways.
横向きにこっち見て
It's ticking.
ちんちんカチカチじゃん
Your pussy is tight, isn't it?
おまんこきっついでしょこれ
Follow me from behind.
後ろからついて
It's slimy.
ぬるぬるだよ
It has a lot of curls.
まんじりいっぱいついてるよ
Chin chin.
ちんちん
Sakura-chan is such a pervert.
さくらちゃんこんな変態だよ
It's really slimy.
ぬるぬるだよ本当に
Kuro-chan's last.
くろちゃん最後
Here you go.
えんろいまんここれほら
Swallow such a big dick.
こんなにでっかいちんちん飲み込んで
That dick feels so good.
そんなちんちん気持ちいいんだ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Hold your legs in your hands like this.
足こうやって自分のお手で抱えて
Let me leave.
おくまいさせてもらいましょう
I'll give it all.
全部だしちゃう
Kuro-chan gives it all.
全部だしちゃうくろちゃん
Kuro-chan was scraping it out with her fingers.
くろちゃん指でかき出してたし
Open your pussy.
まんこ開いて
It's going to be really hard.
めっちゃいっかいだしちゃう
He's a mushy mess.
もろどろたれてるやついし
Scrape it out.
かき出してよ
Kurimobinbinnashi here you go.
くりもびんびんなしこれほら
I ate this with Sakura-chan's manju.
これさくらちゃんのまんじゅうで食べたから
Everything from the bottom.
下から全部
I care about everything.
全部気にするね
Kuro-chan moved quickly.
くろちゃん早く動いたね
I suck big dick.
い っぱいちんこしゃぶす
Was it clean?
きれいにできた?
Properly.
ちゃんと
I was able to do it.
できた
Did Sakura-chan get your attention?
さくらちゃん気を取ってもらった?
The third person is fake.
3人目でっち
It felt amazing.
すごい気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Sakura-chan is really cute.
さ くらちゃんまじでかわいいわ
Will we meet again?
また会ってくれる?
I want to see you again.
また会いたい
Let me try to say it again.
また言っちゃおうとしよう
See you again then.
じゃあまた会おうね
Ask them to say bye-bye.
バイバイしてもらう